[{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984127333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5859,"timeElapsed":55150},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984131384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":59201},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984138820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7434,"timeElapsed":66637},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984148753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9931,"timeElapsed":76570},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984156842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8088,"timeElapsed":84659},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984162884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6039,"timeElapsed":90700},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984166742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3857,"timeElapsed":94559},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984172536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5792,"timeElapsed":100353},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984179577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7041,"timeElapsed":107394},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984206601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":25706,"timeElapsed":134417},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984211653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5050,"timeElapsed":139470},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984217401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5746,"timeElapsed":145218},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984222542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5140,"timeElapsed":150359},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984224882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2339,"timeElapsed":152699},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984231002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":6119,"timeElapsed":158819},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984233522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":161339},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984238944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5420,"timeElapsed":166761},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984240665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":168482},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984247472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5803,"timeElapsed":175289},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984249790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2316,"timeElapsed":177607},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984254177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4386,"timeElapsed":181994},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984263457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9280,"timeElapsed":191274},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984265843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2384,"timeElapsed":193660},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984272435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6592,"timeElapsed":200252},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984274258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1822,"timeElapsed":202075},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984279219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4958,"timeElapsed":207036},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984280817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1596,"timeElapsed":208634},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984290222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":8538,"timeElapsed":218039},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984293405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3183,"timeElapsed":221222},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984296432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3025,"timeElapsed":224249},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984300707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4273,"timeElapsed":228524},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984302372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":230189},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984305701,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3329,"timeElapsed":233518},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984311743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6039,"timeElapsed":239560},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984313555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1810,"timeElapsed":241372},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984319482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5927,"timeElapsed":247299},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984321294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1810,"timeElapsed":249111},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984329022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6085,"timeElapsed":256839},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984331981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":259798},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984334254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2272,"timeElapsed":262071},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984337663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3406,"timeElapsed":265479},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984339272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1608,"timeElapsed":267089},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984342028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2755,"timeElapsed":269845},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984344267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":272084},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984346337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2070,"timeElapsed":274154},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984348362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":276179},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984406197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4836,"timeElapsed":334014},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984411914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5715,"timeElapsed":339730},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984414005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":341822},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984418179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4172,"timeElapsed":345995},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984419789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1609,"timeElapsed":347606},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984422319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":350136},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984423803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1483,"timeElapsed":351620},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984427921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4117,"timeElapsed":355738},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984429306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1382,"timeElapsed":357122},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984433602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3509,"timeElapsed":361419},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984435819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":363636},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984437393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":365210},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984439993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":367810},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984441467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1472,"timeElapsed":369284},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984443705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2238,"timeElapsed":371522},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984445336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1630,"timeElapsed":373153},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984447620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":375437},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984449083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1461,"timeElapsed":376900},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984456181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6309,"timeElapsed":383998},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984460930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4747,"timeElapsed":388747},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984464518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3587,"timeElapsed":392335},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984466756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2236,"timeElapsed":394572},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984468286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1530,"timeElapsed":396103},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984471358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3069,"timeElapsed":399175},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984473270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":401087},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984475453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":403269},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984476791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1338,"timeElapsed":404608},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984481427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3780,"timeElapsed":409244},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984483609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2180,"timeElapsed":411426},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984486410,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2800,"timeElapsed":414227},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984489066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":416883},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984491361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2294,"timeElapsed":419177},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984492789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1426,"timeElapsed":420606},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984495038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":422855},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984496636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1597,"timeElapsed":424453},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984499562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2924,"timeElapsed":427379},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984501136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":428953},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984514254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":12352,"timeElapsed":442071},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984516133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":443950},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984517933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1800,"timeElapsed":445750},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984519732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1797,"timeElapsed":447549},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984521196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1463,"timeElapsed":449013},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984522658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1462,"timeElapsed":450475},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984524031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1371,"timeElapsed":451847},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984526146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":453963},{"subjectID":"8bs2uba3bh","prolificID":"67206083e8af4cf14439ac21","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769c17ffe391b369fbb0144","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734984527979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":455796}]